<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Content on All Your Codebase</title><link>https://allyourcodebase.com/</link><description>Recent content in Content on All Your Codebase</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 17:18:20 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://allyourcodebase.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Gamedev</title><link>https://allyourcodebase.com/gamedev/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 17:18:20 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://allyourcodebase.com/gamedev/</guid><description>Maturity Zig is actively used for game development by both hobbyists for side projects, as well as a few seriously committed individuals who do Zig game development full time.
Libraries and bindings exist for most things, and general purpose engines/frameworks/ecosystems are in early stages of development.
Mach engineGame engine &amp; graphics toolkit for the future. zig-gamedevBuilding game development ecosystem for @ziglang! zero-graphicsA very minimal OpenGL ES 2.0 library for Zig Mach is for creating games, graphical applications, and desktop/mobile/web apps:</description></item><item><title>The Zig Programming Language</title><link>https://allyourcodebase.com/zig/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://allyourcodebase.com/zig/</guid><description>Commonly Asked Questions When will Zig reach v1.0? Zig will be tagged v1 once:
all planned language features have been implemented the full language spec has been published all known bugs have been solved stdlib has gone through a full release cycle without any change If you want to help us move forward faster, consider donating so that we can pay more contributors for their time.
Is Zig made by a big tech company?</description></item><item><title>Web Development</title><link>https://allyourcodebase.com/webdev/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://allyourcodebase.com/webdev/</guid><description>Maturity The Zig Web Development ecosystem is still very immature. At this stage we recommend you consider Zig only if you&amp;rsquo;re interested in looking under the hood of modern web development.
Libraries / tools Databases TigerBeetle is a distributed database for financial transactions written in Zig Sqlite leroycep/sqlite-zig vrishmann/zig-sqlite Redis kristoff-it/zig-okredis HTTP &amp;amp; related ducdetronquito/h11 I/O free state machine implementation of the HTTP/1.1 protocol. Vexu/routez HTTP server written in Zig Vexu/zuri URI parser written in Zig Luukdegram/apple_pie Basic HTTP server implementation in Zig truemedian/hzzp A I/O agnostic HTTP/1.</description></item><item><title>Zig &amp; Other Languages / Ecosystems</title><link>https://allyourcodebase.com/ecosystems/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://allyourcodebase.com/ecosystems/</guid><description>Maturity Zig&amp;rsquo;s ability to empower other languages and ecosystems relies mainly on the Zig compiler toolchain, the most mature component of the Zig project.
Build Systems Bazel motiejus/bazel-zig-cc Languages Elixir ityonemo/zigler Zig NIFs for Elixir! Go Zig Makes Go Cross Compilation Just Work Building SQLite with CGo for (Almost) Every OS JavaScript evanwashere/napi.zig fubark/zig-v8 pluvial/vite-plugin-zig pluvial/node-zig npm install @ziglang/cli Python ziglang/zig-pypi pip install ziglang Rust messense/cargo-zigbuild Improved Rust cross-compilation support</description></item><item><title>Zig on Embedded</title><link>https://allyourcodebase.com/embedded/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://allyourcodebase.com/embedded/</guid><description>Maturity // TODO
Microzig // TODO
Libraries / Tools // TODO</description></item></channel></rss>